{"data":[{"question":"I haven't enjoyed myself so many for years.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"haven't","b":"myself","c":"many","d":"for","answer":"3","explain":"- So many for-> for so many","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Immediately after his arrival, things went to wrong.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Immediately","b":"arrival","c":"things","d":"to","answer":"4","explain":"- To->x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"You can eat as much as you like at the newly lunch-bar.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"eat","b":"much","c":"at","d":"newly","answer":"4","explain":"- Newly-> new","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"It takes a ship approximately eight hours to complete the trip through the canal and cost an average of fifteen thousands dollars.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"approximately","b":"complete","c":"through","d":"thousands","answer":"4","explain":"- Thousands-> thousand","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"You think that fat people is always jolly, but you are wrong.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"that","b":"is","c":"jolly","d":"wrong","answer":"2","explain":"- Is-> are","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"My parents prefer to live in the countryside because they dislike the noisy and traffic of the city.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"prefer","b":"in","c":"dislike","d":"noisy","answer":"4","explain":"- Noisy-> noise","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"I have to use the public telephone because my is out of order.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"use","b":"public","c":"my","d":"of","answer":"3","explain":"- Mine->my","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"There have been an increase in road-accidents in the last few years.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"have","b":"increase","c":"road-accidents","d":"few","answer":"1","explain":"- Have->has","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"It began to rain when the manager had got out of the office this morning.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"began","b":"when","c":"had got","d":"this","answer":"3","explain":"- Had got-> had gotten","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"When the boy was twelve, his father died of a dangerous diseases.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"When","b":"was","c":"of","d":"diseases","answer":"4","explain":"- Diseases-> disease","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"}]}